(Leonard's Mother:)Oh.
(Beverley:)Your Uncle Floyd died.
(Leonard:)Oh, my God. What happened?
(Beverley:)His heart stopped beating.
(Beverley:)I have to urinate.
(Sheldon:)What a remarkable woman.
(Leonard:)Yeah, I... I thought
you guys might hit it off.
(Sheldon:)I envy you your childhood.
(Leonard:)I hate to tell you...
(Leonard:)...but the only warm memories I have
of my childhood are of my Uncle Floyd.
(Sheldon:)You're clearly misremembering. Your mother
is brilliant, analytical, insightful.
(Sheldon:)I'm betting she never hit you with a Bible
because you wouldn't eat Brussels sprouts.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, you don't give
your mother enough credit.
(Leonard:)She's warm, she's loving,
she doesn't glue electrodes to your head...
(Leonard:)...to measure your brain waves
while potty training.
(Sheldon:)You were lucky.
(Sheldon:)When I was a kid, if I wanted an EEG,
I had to attach my own electrodes.